

Team lead

Santa clarita -, Ca. 91321 jasmineestavan@gmail.com

Dedicated customer service professional with history of meeting company goals utilizing consistent and organized practices. Skilled in working under pressure and adapting to new situations and challenges to best enhance the organizational brand, with over 7 years of successful experience in customer service.

Professional Experience

Team lead

No fear, Palmdale, Ca | February 2013 - March 2015

- Maintained excellent attendance record, consistently arriving to work on time.
- Worked to maintain outstanding attendance record, consistently arriving to work ready to start immediately.
- Conducted research, gathered information from multiple sources and presented results.
- · Helped customers complete purchases, locate items and join reward programs.
- · Collected and authorized payments of guests.
- Performed cash, card and check transactions to complete customer purchases.

Lab associate

Quest diagnostics, Valencia, ca | June 2015 - May 2018

- · Identified issues, analyzed information and provided solutions to problems.
- Completed paperwork, recognizing discrepancies and promptly addressing for resolution.
- · Participated in team-building activities to enhance working relationships.
- · Oversaw daily operations to ensure high levels of productivity.

Sales assistant

Telehealth Van, los angeles, ca | February 2019 - Present

- · Worked to maintain outstanding attendance record, consistently arriving to work ready to start immediately.
- · Carried out day-day-day duties accurately and efficiently.
- Quickly learned new skills and applied them to daily tasks, improving efficiency and productivity.
- · Served customers and followed outlined steps of service.
- · Oversaw daily operations to ensure high levels of productivity.

Education

Associate of Science in Psychology College of the canyons at Valencia February 2013 - May 2016

Key Skills

- · Reading comprehension
- Multitasking abilities
- · Computer skills
- · Customer service
- · MS Office
- · Basic math · Leadership
- Teambuilding
- Written Communication
- Flexible & Adaptable
- · computer knowledge